The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Let me see
how you will escape this time.
Master !
Bunch of fools...
Xu Mu may be strong,
but he's only at Corporeal Yang.
How could he possibly defeat this person ?
You
can't escape.
A physical form of Divine Sense
to trap me in a cage ?
I can't teleport !?
Wind !
Call the Wind ?
What's your relationship with Celestial Emperor Bai Fan !?
Lands Collapse !
This is one of my strands of Ji Realm ?
So you really were able to subdue it.
Go !
Master Carefree's Withered Dao Pair ?
Let me see
what else you've got.
A Rain Celestial Sword !
You're a very interesting Qi Refiner.
This man can brush off my attacks
as if they were nothing.
Now,
I have to use the Blood Ancestor's blood body's origin energy.
It's all or nothing.
Explode !
Call the Wind !
Not enough !
It's still...
not enough !
Explode !
Thankfully, I didn't make a move that day.
If I had, I wouldn't have lasted an instant
against this black wind.
Master...
Did you win ?
There's no way he was defeated just like that.
Not dead ?
He's not dead !
Bai Fan's celestial spell,
Qing Shuang's celestial sword,
Master Carefree's artifact...
Tell me your name.
You
are worthy being remembered.
Little guy fated with me,
don't be in such a hurry.
This old man can't come here right now,
so let me borrow your body.
It's him !
This old man
will treat you to a good show.
Enough with the nonsense.
So what if you're a Celestial Lord ?
Also,
your current cultivation
isn't even on par with a Celestial King.
You can use the power of the world ?
You're not that Qi Refiner from before !
Who
are you !?
You don't know who I am.
But I
know exactly who you are.
I...
Who am I ?
Celestial Burning Flame,
rise !
Blaze !
Wang Lin's\NSea of Consciousness
A single thought can draw upon the power of the world ?
Not bad.
Among the later generations of Qi Refiners,
someone has actually reached this level.
Refine !
Ji... Realm !
This is bad,
if his Origin Soul gets scattered
and he flees,
I'll die for sure.
That's some serious strength.
This Ji Realm
is way stronger than the previous one.
That was close.
This Ji Realm is indeed astounding.
I didn't expect that after being sealed for so many years,
he would still be this strong.
However,
I didn't make all those preparations in vain.
Little one,
you're not bad at all.
So this is Master's true power !
Who...
Who the hell is he exactly ?
You
are strong.
However, right now,
I need to replenish my strength.
Run away !
I won't let you devour anymore.
Gather !
Get away from here !
Scatter !
Power of the world ?
I'm not dead ?
You're so annoying !
Aren't you ashamed ?
To have fallen so low as to devour juniors to recover your cultivation...
If you have even a shred of pride,
then face me in an honorable battle,
Celestial Lord Qing Shui !
You...
What did you say ?!
I said that
you are the crown prince of the Clear Water State,
the disciple of Celestial Emperor Bai Fan,
Celestial Lord Qing Shui !
It's him !
Impossible...
Impossible !
Qing Shui is my enemy !
The heir of the Clear Water State
can't even remember his own name,
it really is sad.
I...
am not Qing Shui !
No wonder he knows the Lands Collapse spell.
How did he end up like this ?
You want to devour but I won't let you !
Help me !
You can go.
Wait for me !
Go home !
Back then, after being enlightened by Master,
I condensed all my lifetime of insights into this thunder bolt
for this moment !
Save him !
Master !
Are you ever going to stop !?
Celestial spell...
Disappear...
Scatter !
Damn it...
That was a huge loss.
I really messed up this time...
You
are courting death !
I'm not fighting you anymore,
catch me if you can !
So you are luring me ?
Very well.
Once I find your true body,
I'll use you
to make up for the origin energy of those thousands of cultivators !
He's using such a massive amount of origin energy
but not running out ?
It turns out he's only using a tiny bit from his own Origin Soul,
and is constantly drawing upon the energy of the world.
Spatial Bending...
Although I understand the basics,
I'm far from being able to do it as naturally as breathing
without any effort.
Only by merging deeply with the world
can one truly glimpse
and even wield
the power of the laws of the world.
Celestial Descent Platform\NThunder Celestial Realm
Celestial Descent Platform ?
It's the former capital of the Thunder Celestial Realm,
and where the Ancient Celestials would descend.
What's his purpose
in leading me here ?
Every time Qing Shui takes a heavy blow,
his form shifts closer to his peak
and he gets stronger.
The old man is clearly aware of it
but seems to be deliberately facilitating it.
Could it be...
that he actually intends to guide Qing Shui back to his peak ?
Little one,
I'm going ahead of you.
Whatever he's plotting,
he'll certainly return.
I need to hold on.
Heavenly Chop !
If that junior doesn't show up,
then I'll just have to devour you first !
I already used half of the Blood Ancestor's blood body.
There's no way to retreat.
You want to kill me
but it won't be that easy !
The Mountains and Rivers Painting ?
It's nothing but an imitation.
I spent 1000 years
comprehending the real painting.
With your cultivation,
even with the true painting in hand,
breaking it
would still be just as easy.
This is...
What an incredible formation !
Save me !
He's going to refine the entire Thunder Celestial Realm
into an artifact ?
After tens of thousands of years of planning
and countless trips in and out,
I finally refined the Thunder Celestial Realm
into an artifact !
Cultivators of the world,
who among you can be as bold as me !?
We cultivators of Allheaven will cross the barrier between Star Systems !
We will no longer be bound by Allheaven Stones !
Master Zhongxuan,
when you forced me to leave back then,
I told you
that one day
I would lead millions of cultivators from the Allheaven Star System
to crush the Cultivation Alliance !
He technically isn't refining the "entire" Thunder Celestial Realm but half of it.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.